Curriculum Vitae

Henry Meager

Email: henry.meager@gmail.com

<u>About Me</u>

I am 24 years old. I am friendly, cheerful and reliable. I finished school in the summer of 2017 with 3 A levels. Since then I have worked, traveled and obtained my BASI Level 2 Ski Instructor's qualification. Much of my work experience has been in the hospitality industry, the majority of which has been in customer facing roles, however now as I have recently finished my coding bootcamp, I'm keen to land my first role inside of the tech space.

Education

<u>iO Academy - September 2023 - December 2023</u>

I have recently completed a coding bootcamp with iO Academy. The focus of the bootcamp was to cover the fundamentals of web development, in order to make each student readily employable. Throughout the course, we covered: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React, PHP and Laravel. Alongside learning these skills, we have also made projects such as: Our portfolio websites, a book swapping app using React, PHP and SQL and a collector's website using PHP. The course also utilised the sprint methodology, with daily stand-ups and weekly sprint reviews during project weeks, to match a real working scenario as closely as possible.

Bloxham School, Bloxham - Sept 2012 to June 2017

During my time at Bloxham school I achieved A levels in French, English Literature and Business Studies.

Beachborough School, Westbury - April 2002 - June 2012

Interests

Outside of school and work one of my favourite hobbies is to play chess. I was taught how to play when I was young, and have now rediscovered my love for the game, spending a good portion of my free time on studying tactics and playing games online. During the winter months of the year I also love to go skiing. Although I've not gone as much as I'd have liked these past few years, I still hold a great passion and skill for the sport, hence my instructing qualification.

Recent History

Baumhaus Ltd - January 2023 - September 2023

My time at Baumhaus was spent as a returns operative inside of a warehouse. My main job was to manage the excel spreadsheets and photography of any returned items, and ensuring that everything was in order for them to be sent off to the main office and listed on to eBay.

<u>Sitel - September 2022 - December 2022</u>

During my short tenure with Sitel, I worked in the customer support team for John Lewis over the busy Christmas period. I was based inside the small electronics team, meaning my main role was to help troubleshoot issues that John Lewis customers had had with small electronic devices such as phones, tablets or even laptops.

The Orangery - May 2021 - January 2022

At The Orangery, I worked as a waiter where it was my role to provide the best service possible for the visitors of Blenheim Palace.

<u>Cotswold Organs - December 2020 - May 2021 / January 2022 - September 2022</u>

This is my father's company which I have been working for, helping with the installation of organs in churches and people's homes. My main tasks have been to assist in carrying heavy loads, building scaffolding towers and providing general assistance wherever required.

Nando's - April 2019 - December 2020

As a Nandoca, I worked as a team member at Nando's. Whether it was operating the tills, working on the grills or waiting tables, I was always expected to give my all as a representative of the brand and to make the experience as enjoyable as possible for the customers. During my time at Nando's I learnt valuable skills such as: the ability to work during busy periods under high amounts of pressure; great customer service; and how to function well as part of a team. I left Nando's having been furloughed for months and at a time when my father required assistance in his new business.

Meribel - February 2019 - March 2019 (with SnowSkool)

Completed my BASI Level 2 Ski Instructor's qualification in Les Allues, Meribel, France.

<u>Travelling – October 2018 – December 2018</u>

During these months I travelled with family to New Zealand, visiting Wellington and Auckland. I also spent time in France with family over Christmas.

Miller & Carter - January 2018 – September 2018

At Miller & Carter, I worked as a dessert chef (save for some time out for ski training as set out below) where I had the role of plating desserts to make them presentable to customers. It was important to get them out on time, especially during the busier periods. Teamwork and efficiency were necessary to be able to keep everything running smoothly in the kitchen.

Meribel – January 2018 – March 2018 (with SnowSkool)

I spent 9 weeks in Meribel finishing my BASI Level 1 and training for my BASI Level 2 ski instructor's qualification.

Other Work Experience

<u>Viscount Classical Organs Limited – occasional work</u>

I have, on odd occasions, helped my father (who worked for this company) in installing and removing organs that the company has hired for events / occasions.

Bamboo Marketing (Worcester) Limited - October 2016

I undertook work experience with this automotive marketing company. I was responsible for contacting customers by telephone and taking inbound calls. My main task was to advise customers on servicing events due for their vehicles and follow up calls after such events. Good interpersonal and communication skills were essential to this role.